Finding Aid for the Arthur William Ingersoll Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Ingersoll - student folders
  - Yusk, John Francis Fr. 9/59
WHITE, H. C. (Dow Chemical Company) - 3 (1948-50)
WHITMORE, Frank C. (Northwestern University) - 2 (1926)
WILDER, Pelham, Jr. (Harvard University) - 1 (1949)
WILLARD, Harry L. (Corn Products Refining Company) - 3 (1948)
WINSTEIN, S. - 1 (1945)
ZELINSKI, Robert P. (DePaul University)- 1 (1951)